Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
- Series IV. Professional Papers Writings Books
  - R.S. Marcus and J.F. Reintjes- Computer Interface (Conis) (Box 47, Folder 71)
  - Marden, E.C. and Koller, H.R.- A Survey of Computer Programs for Chemical Information Searching (Box 47, Folder 72)
  - Merek, Wiktor, A decomposition of Information Systems (Box 47, Folder 73)
  - Margolis, J., Citation Indexing and Evaluation of Scientific Papers (Box 47, Folder 74)
  - Mark IV Programs (Box 47, Folder 75)
  - Mark I- Mark IV- Engineering Notes (Box 47, Folder 76)
  - Checking Routines for Mark IV Function routines (Box 47, Folder 77)
  - Mark IV (Box 47, Folder 78)
  - Mark I- IBM Automatic Sequence Controlled Calculator (Box 47, Folder 79)
  - Markus, John- "State of the Art of Published Indexes" (Box 47, Folder 80)
  - Markuson, Barbara Evans- An Overview of Library Systems and Automation (Box 47, Folder 81)
  - Markuson, B.E.- System Development Study for Library of Congress Automation Program (Box 47, Folder 82)
  - M.E. Maron, Sean Curry, Paul Thompson- Inductive Search System (Box 47, Folder 83)
  - M.E. Maron- Depth of Indexing (Box 47, Folder 84)
  - Maron, M.E. and Shoffner, R.M.- The Study of Context: An Overview (Box 47, Folder 85)
  - Maron, M.E. and Shoffner, R.M.- The Study of Context: An Overview (Box 47, Folder 86)
  - Maron, M.E.- "On Cybernetic, Information Processing and Thinking" RAND Corporation (Box 47, Folder 87)
  - Maron, M.E.- Automatic Indexing: An Experimental Inquiry (Box 47, Folder 88)
  - M.E. Maron- Associative Search Techniques (Box 47, Folder 89)
  - M.E. Maron and J.L. Kuhns- On Relevance, Prob.Indexing and IR (Box 47, Folder 90)
  - M.E. Maron (AM Pestersen) Meaning of "About" (Box 47, Folder 91)
  - Marthaler, Marc P. "Current Research in Automatic Scientific Documentation" (Box 47, Folder 92)
  - C. Martinez- An Expert System for Machine Indexing (Box 47, Folder 93)
  - Martyn, John, "Literature Searching by Research Scientists" (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Mason, Ellsworth--The Great Gas Bubble Prick't; or Computers Revealed-by a Gentleman of Quality (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Masquerade (Marathon Oil) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Masterman, Margaret, Man-aided Computer Translation from English into French using an On-Line System to Manipulate a Bi-Lingual Conceptual Dictionary, or Thesaurus (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Masterman, Margaret, and Needham, R.M., Specification and Sample Operations of a Model Thesaurus (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Mathis, Betty A., Rush, James E. and Young, Carol E.: Improvement of Automatic Abstracts by the Use of Structural Analysis (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Matzek, Richard A., Network Concepts-Four Points of View (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - M. Mauldin and J. Carbonell, Knowledge Based Information Retrieval (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - M. Mauldin; Indexing with Knowledge Base (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - May, C., Evaluation of Search Methods (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Z. Mazur, Inverted Files based on Weighted Thesaurus (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - McAllester, D., Artificial Intelligence (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - McCarn, Davis C-227, The Biomedical Communications Network (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - McCarn, Davis B. and Leiter, Joseph, On-Line Services in Medicine and Beyond (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - McCarton, Edward F., Creativity, Computers and Copyright (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - McCarthy, John, Programs with Common Sense (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - McConlogue, Keren, and Simmons, R.F., "Analyzing English Syntax with a Pattern-Learning Parser" SP-1950 Feb.5, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - D. McDermott, Critique of Pure Reason (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - D. McGregor and J.R. Malone, Information Retrieval with Recursively Enumerated Sets (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - M.J. McGill and T. Noreault SIRE Experiments (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - M. McGill, M. Koll, and T. Koreault, Document Ranking (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - M.J. McGill and J. Huitfeldt, Techniques of Information Retrieval (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - McGill, Michael J.--Knowledge and Information Spaces: Membership and Viewpoints (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - J.W. McInroy, Automatic Extracting (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - McKenna, M. and Zelter, D., Dynamic Simulation of Autonomous Legged Locomotion (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - K.R. McKeown, Text System (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - K.R. McKeown, Text System for Natural Language (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - E.J. McKinin et. al., Medline/Full-Text Research Project (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - McNeill, J.W. and Wetherell, C.S., Bibliographic Data as an Aid to Document Retrieval (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - C.T. Meadow, Interactive Database Search (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Mealy, George H., Operating Systems (Excerpts) (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - MedLars (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - J.R. Meehan, The Metanovel (T/oni) (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Medlars System (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Meetham, A.R., "Preliminary Studies for Machine Generated Index Vocabularies (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Meetham, A.R., Communication Theory and the Evaluation of Information Retrieval Systems (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Meetham, A.R., Probabilistic Pairs and Groups of Words in a Text (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Meister, D. and Sullivan, D.J., Evaluation of User Reactions to a Prototype On-Line Information Retrieval System (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Melchuk, I.A., "Automatic Analysis of Texts: Russiar Language Materials" JPRS: 25,849 11 August 1964, TT: 64-41120 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - Melton, Jessica S., "English Language Problems: Mech. Search Techniques" (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - Melton, Jessica S., Automatic Processing of Metallurgical Abstracts for the Purpose of Information Retrieval (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Melzer, Harry Z., Semantic Interpretation for Question Answering Systems: A tutorial (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Memory Based Reasoning (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - MENUS (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - T.H. Merrett, Patricia (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - D. Metzler, T. Noreault, Dependency Parsing (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - M. Mesteer, Fast Data Finder (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - J.G. Meunier, Enhanced Representation of Content (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - Meyer Ernst, "Eine Maschine zur Verschlusselung chemischer Strukturformeln fur die Dokumentation" (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - Meyer, E., "Eine topologische Kurzdorstellung chemischer Strukturformein fur die Dokumentation mit elek" (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - Meyer, Von Ernst, Zur Mechanisierung der Dokumentation in der Chemie (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - Meyer-Uhlenried, K.H., "Automatic Documentation and Machine Translating" (Box 48, Folder 52)
  - Michael, D.N.: Speculations on the Relation of the Computer to Individual Freedom and the Right to Privacy (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - Michaelson, Herbert B., "Achieving a more disciplined Literature" (Box 48, Folder 54)
  - Microfilm The Role of Micrographics in Modern Information Systems (Box 48, Folder 55)
  - Microfilm Survey (Computer Output) (Box 48, Folder 56)
  - F. Baskett, Microprocessors: From Desktops to Supercomputers (Box 48, Folder 57)
  - Mikhaylov, A.I./Chernyy, A.I./Gilyarevskiy, "Informatics--A New Name for Scientific Information Theory" (Box 48, Folder 58)
  - J. Gormly Miller, Planning and Compilation of a Thesaurus for indexing, abstracting and retrieval of documents and information on public sector labor relations (Box 48, Folder 59)
  - Miller, James G. EDUCOM: Interuniversity Communications Council (Box 48, Folder 60)
  - Miller, P.L.--A Locally Organized Parser for Spoken Input (Box 48, Folder 61)
  - Mills, J., "Classification as an Indexing Device" (Box 48, Folder 62)
  - R. Minch, Reference Points (Box 48, Folder 63)
  - Micro Computers (Box 48, Folder 64)
  - Mini Computer Survey (Box 48, Folder 65)
  - Minieka, Edward--On Computing Sets of Shortest Paths in a Graph (Box 48, Folder 66)
  - Minitel (Box 48, Folder 67)
  - Minker, Jack, Peltola, Eero, and Wilson, Gerald, Document Retrieval Experiments Using Cluster Analysis (Box 48, Folder 68)
  - Minker, Jack, Wilson, G.A., Zimmerman, An Evaluation of Query Expansion by the Addition of Clustered Terms for a Document Reference System (Box 48, Folder 69)
  - Minsky, M. and Papert, S., A Review of Perceptrons: An Introduction to Computational Geometry by H.D. Block (Box 48, Folder 70)
  - J. Minker, Science, Sharansky and Soviets (Box 48, Folder 71)
  - Minsky, Naftaly: Toward "Intelligent" Rotating Storage Devices (Box 48, Folder 72)
  - A. Moffat, J. Zobel, Memory Efficient Ranking (Box 48, Folder 73)
  - M. Mohr, Problems on Retrieval Evaluation (Box 48, Folder 74)
  - Montgomery, Christine--Linguistics and Information Science (Box 48, Folder 75)
  - Montgomery, C. and Swanson, D.R., Machinelike Indexing by People (Box 48, Folder 76)
  - Mooers, Calvin N.--Computer Software and Copyright (Box 48, Folder 77)
  - Mooers, Calvin N., The Application of Simple Pattern Inclusion Selection to Large-Scale Information Retrieval Systems (Box 48, Folder 78)
  - Mooers, C.N., Information Retrieval Bibliography of Papers and Publications 1947-1956 (Box 48, Folder 79)
  - Mooers, Calvin N., Part II: Seven System Models (Box 48, Folder 80)
  - C.N. Mooers, Informatin Retrieval on Structured Contents (Box 48, Folder 81)
  - Mooers, Calvin N., The Intensive Sample Test (Box 48, Folder 82)
  - C.N. Mooers, Mooers' Law (Box 48, Folder 83)
  - Mooers, C.N., The Next Twenty Years In Information Retrieval: Some Goals and Predictions (Box 48, Folder 84)
  - Mooers, Calvin N., TRAC, A Procedure-Describing Language for the Reactive Typewriter (Box 48, Folder 85)
  - Mooers, Calvin N., "Wanted: A Reactive Typewriter" (Box 48, Folder 86)
  - Mooers, C.N., Some Mathematical Fundamentals of the Use of Symbols in Information Retrieval (Box 48, Folder 87)
  - Moors, Calvin N., "Zatocoding and Developments in Information Retrieval" (Box 48, Folder 88)
  - Mooers, C.N., Part I: Extension of Pattern Inclusion Selection (Box 48, Folder 89)
  - Mooers, C.N., Zatocoding for Punched Cards (Box 48, Folder 90)
  - C.N. Mooers, Retrieval B4 Paoximity Transforms, 2TB 113 (Box 48, Folder 91)
  - Mooers, C.N., Zatocoding Applied to Mechanical Organization of Knowledge (Box 48, Folder 92)
  - Kahr, A.S., Moore, Edward F. and Wang, Hao, "Entscheidungsproblem Reduced to the AEA Case" Harvard University (Box 48, Folder 93)
  - Moore, Edward F., "Machine Models of Self-Reproduction" (Box 48, Folder 94)
  - Moore, Edward F., "An Academic Year at Cambridge, Mass" (Box 48, Folder 95)
  - Moore, E.F., "Problems of Research Interest in Information Retrieval" (Box 48, Folder 96)
  - Moore, Robert T., "A Screening Method for Large Information Retrieval Systems" (Box 48, Folder 97)
  - Moreau, R., "Linquistique et Telecommunications" "Quelque Remarques-Codage Auto." (Box 48, Folder 98)
  - H. Morgan, and R. Gerritsen, Metrics for Data Bases (Box 48, Folder 99)
  - Morgan, H.L.: The Generation of a Unique Machine Description for Chemical Structures A Technique Developed at Chemical Abstracts Service (Box 48, Folder 100)
  - A.H. Morris and Others, Automatic Text Condensing (Box 48, Folder 101)
  - J.M. Morris, Traversing Binary Trees Simply and Cheaply (Box 48, Folder 102)
  - Robert T. Morris, Computer Worm (Box 48, Folder 103)
  - Morrison, Donald R, Patricia-Practical Algorithm to Retrieve Information Coded in Alphanumeric (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - J.M. Morrissey, D.J. Harper and C.J. Van Rijsbergen, Interactive Query (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Morse, Philip M., Measures of Library Effectiveness (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Morse, Philip, On Browsing: The Use of Search Theory in the Search for Information (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Mosaic and the World Wide Web (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Moser, Andreas, Interactive Techniques in Automatic Document Retrieval (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Moser, Andreas Hermann, Informations-Speicherung und Ruckgewinnung mit SMART vergleischende Dorstellung und erganzende Kommentierung mit Rucksicht... (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Moser, Andreas H., Some Retrieval Experiments Using German Common Language Documents (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - W. Moskovich, Quantitative Linguistion (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Mosteller, Frederick, "An Authorship Problem" (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Motzkin, Dalia--The Use of Normal Multiplication Tables for Information Storage and Retrieval (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - A. Mowshowitz, Social Issues in Computing (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - A. Mowshowitz, Ethics and Cultural Integration (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Moyne, J.A., Information Retrieval and Natural Language (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Moyne, J.A., Proto-RELADES SAMPLE OUTPUT (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Mulford, James, and Ridall, Richard, Data Compression Techniques for Economic Processing of Large Commercial Files (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Muller, von Bernd S.--Untersuchungen zum InhaltserschlieBungssystem TELDEX (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Grammer (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Multidimensional Scaling (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Multi Lingual Text Filtering (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Multimedia (Audio and Image Processing) (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Multimedia Documents (see hypertext) (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Multi Processing (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Mumps Data Management System (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Murphy, R.W., "The IBM 9900 Special Index Analyzer" (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Davis, M., and Murray, D., File Organization for an On-line Retrieval System (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Murray, D.M., A Clustered File Organization for Document Retrieval Systems (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Murray, Daniel M., File Organization Schemes (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Murray, D.M., Centroid Definitions for Clustered File Organizations (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Murray, Daniel M., A Scatter Storage Scheme for Dictionary Lookups (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - F. Murtagh, Hierarchical Clustering (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Computer Music (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Museum (Files, Recordings) (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Myers, John Computers and the Searching of Law Texts in England and North America: A Review of the State of the Art (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - J. Mylopoulos et. al., A Language for Database (Taxis) (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - O. Nacke, Informetrie A New Discipline (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Nagib A. Shamji, Extended Verson (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - N. Naffah and A. Karmouch, Agora-Multimedia Messages (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Naive Semantics, K. Dahlgren and J. McDowell (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - BHAT, U.N., NANCE, Richard, Korfhage Robert, Information Networks: A Probabilistic Model for Hierarchical Message Transfer (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Nance, Richard E., Analytical Model of a Library Network (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - D. Navinchandra, Katia P. Sycara, and S. Narasimhan, A Transformational Approach to Case-Based Synthesis (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - NASA Introducing NASA's RECON (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - National Academy of Sciences, "The Metallurgical Searching Service-An Evaluation" (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - National Bureau of Standards Complete Clear Text Representation of Scientific Documents in Machine-Readable Form (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - National Library of Medicine (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - NCLIS Public Sector/Private Sector (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - National Commission on Libraries C-467 Congressional Records May 1969 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - (Box 49, Folder D.H.D. Warren, Natural Lanuage Queries)
  - Natural Language Analysis (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - J.F. Allen, Plans, Goals and Natural Language (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Natural Language Query Processor (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Natural Language Processing (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Nauchno-Teknicheskaya Informatsiya Series 1, No.5, pp.3-7, 1974 V.M. Solomin-Shachina, Vinnikov etc. Efficency Evaluation (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - NAUR, Peter, Programming Languages, Natural Languages and Mathematics (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - University of Nebraska (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - R.M. Needaam, Applications of Theory of Clumps (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - Needham, R.M., Automatic Classification in Linguistics (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - Needham, R.M./ Jones, R. Sparck, "Keywords and Clumps" (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - Needham, R.M., Miller, A.H.J., and Jones, K.Sparck, "The Information Retrieval System of the Cambridge Language Research Unit" (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - Needham, R.M., "The Theory of Clumps II" (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - K.J. Neff, Generation of Bohiness Letters (Box 49, Folder 62)
  - Negoita, C.V., Dr., Linear and Nonlinear Information Retrieval Systems (Box 49, Folder 63)
  - Negus, A.E., and Hall, J.L., Towards an Effective On-Line Reference Retrieval System (Box 49, Folder 64)
  - M.J. Nelson, Correlation of Term Usage (Box 49, Folder 65)
  - Nelson, H. Wayne, Simulation (Box 49, Folder 66)
  - Network Management (D. Bernard from Computing Surveys) (Box 49, Folder 67)
  - J.S. Quarterman and J.C. Hoskins, Notable Computer Networks (Box 49, Folder 68)
  - R.W. Sanders, Networking (Box 49, Folder 69)
  - Neural Networks (Box 49, Folder 70)
  - Neville, H.H., Thesaurus Reconciliation (Box 49, Folder 71)
  - A. Newell and D.A. Waterman, Auto Protocol Analysis (Box 49, Folder 72)
  - Newell, Allan, "Some Problems of Basic Organization in Problem Solving Programs" (Box 49, Folder 73)
  - Newitt, J.W., and Odarchenko, A., Dictionary-Program for Stenotype Transcription (Box 49, Folder 74)
  - Newman, Simon, "Problems in Mechanizing the Search in Examining Patent Applications" (Box 49, Folder 75)
  - Patent Office, "Storage and Retrieval Of Contents of Technical Literature", S. Newman (Box 49, Folder 76)
  - Patent Office, "Organization of Chemical Disclosures for Mechanized Retrieval", S. Newman (Box 49, Folder 77)
  - Patent Office, "Advances in Mechanization of Patent Searching", S. Newman (Box 49, Folder 78)
  - Patent Office, "A Punched Card System for Searching Steroid Compounds", S. Newman (Box 49, Folder 79)
  - Nichols, A.J., and Reiter, A., "Generalized Software for On-Line Storage and Retrieval" Lockheed Palo Alto Research Laboratory (Box 49, Folder 80)
  - Nicolaus, John J., "The Automated Approach to Technical Information Retrieval" (Box 49, Folder 81)
  - J. Nie, Information Retrieval Model Based on Modal Logic (Box 49, Folder 82)
  - Niehoff, R.T.--Development of an Integrated Energy Vocabulary and the Possibilities for On-Line Subject Switching (Box 49, Folder 83)
  - Nielsen, N.R., Analysis of Some Time-Sharing Techniques (Box 49, Folder 84)
  - Nielsen, P., A Qualitative Approach to Mechanical Constraint (Box 49, Folder 85)
  - Nievergelt J. and Faarrar, J.C., What Machines Can and Cannot Do (Box 49, Folder 86)
  - Noel, J.: Le role de la definition dans une etude semantique preparatoire a l'indexation mecanisee (Box 49, Folder 87)
  - Noel J., Semantics at the 1968 Linguistic Institute (Box 49, Folder 88)
  - Noel, Jacques, Automatic Analysis of English Abstracts for the Purpose of Information Retrieval (Box 49, Folder 89)
  - Nolan, J.J., "Principles of Information Storage and Retrieval Using a Large Scale Random Access Memory" (Box 49, Folder 90)
  - T. Noreault, M. Koll, and M. McGill, Automatic Ranked Output in SIRE (Box 49, Folder 91)
  - Normal Forms (Box 49, Folder 92)
  - J. Nievergelt, H. Hinterberger, and K.C. Sevcik, The Grid File (Box 49, Folder 93)
  - Nobel Prize (Matthew Effect) (Box 49, Folder 94)
  - E. Nodtvedt, Office Automation (Box 49, Folder 95)
  - North of Nell Condominium (Box 49, Folder 96)
  - W. Nugent, Compression Word Coding (Box 49, Folder 97)
  - Object Oriented Program (Box 49, Folder 98)
  - OCLC Inc (Box 49, Folder 99)
  - O'Connor, John J., Information Retrieval by UNIAC and by UNIVAC-Produced Non-Mechanized System Part I (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - O'Connor, John, "Mechanized Indexing Methods and their Testing" (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - O'Connor, John: Automatic Subject Recognition in Scientific Papers: An Empirical Study (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - O'Connor, John: Correlation of Indexing Headings and Title Words in Three Medical Indexing Systems (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - O'Connor, John, "A Manual of Experiments in Documentation" Curriculum for Information Sciences (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - O'Connor, John, "Document Grouping" (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - O'Connor, John, The Scan-Column Index (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - O'Connor, John, Some Independent Agreements and Resolved Disagreements About Answer-Providing Documents (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - O'Connor, John, Text Searching Retrieval of Answer-Sentences and Other Answer-Passages (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - O'Connor, John, Retrieval of Answer-Sentences and Answer-Figures from Papers by Text Searching (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - J. O'Connor, Answer Passage Retrieval (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - O'Connor, John, Retrieval of Answer-Providing Documents (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - J. O'Connor, Retrieval of Answer-Passages from Papers (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - O'Connor, John, Answer-Providing Documents: Some Inference Descriptions and Text-Searching Retrieval Results (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - O'Connor, J., Opinion Paper, Some Questions Concerning "Information Need" (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - J. O'Connor, Answer-Passage Retrieval (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - J. O'Connor, Citing Statements (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - J. O'Connor, Biomedical Citing Statements (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - O'Connor, John: Some Remarks on Mechanized Indexing and Some Small-Scale Empirical Results (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - J. O'Connor, Relevance Disagreements (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - OCR (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - R.N. Oddy, Information Retrieval Through Man-Machine (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - A.G. Oettinger, Automatic Processing of Natural and Formal Languages (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Oettinger, A.G., Automatic Syntactic Analysis and the Pushdown Store (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - A.G. Oettinger, A Bull's Eye View (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Oettinger, A.G., "An Essay in Information Retrieval" or "The Birth of a Myth" (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - A.G., Oettinger, Information Resources (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Libraries and Information Technology (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Oettinger, A.G., et. al., Linguistic Methods for Compiling and Updating the H.A. Dictionary (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Oettinger, A.G., Linguistics and Mathematics (presented to Joshua Whatmough) (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - A.G. Oettinger, Information Resources (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Oettinger, A.G., The Mechanization of Stock Transfer (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Oettinger, Anthony G., The Myths of Educational Technology (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Oettinger, A.G., Account Identification for Automatic Data Processing (ACM Journal 1957) (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - National Symposium on Machine Translation Papers Univ. of California, L.A., Cal., A.G. Oettinger (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Oettinger, A.G., The Producer Payroll of the H.P. Hood Company (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Oettinger, A.G., The Programming Problem (talk in Washington 1957) (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Oettinger, Anthony G., "The State of the Art of Automatic Language Translation: An Appraisal" (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Oettinger, Anthony, G., Statement Prepared for Submission to the Subcommittee on Patents Trademarks, and Copyrights (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Oettinger, Anthony G., "A Study for the Design of an Automatic Dictionary" (AFK) (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - A.G. Oettinger, Technical Aids to Creative Thought (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Oettinger, A.G., "A Trip to the Soviet Union" (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Oettinger, Anthony G., A Vision of Technology and Education (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Oettinger, A., Will Technology Help Learning? (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Office Automation (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - Bulletin de Liaison de la Recherche en Informatique et Automatique (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - SIGOA Conference on Office Information Systems (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - Office Automation/IR (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - Ogden, S. and Wadsworth, N., On-line Graphics at the University of Utah (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - Ohlman, H., Educational Computer Trends in the Cemrel Region Analysis and Recommendations (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - Lee Ohringer, "Progress in Computerized Typesetting" (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - M.S. Ohwovoriole, and B. Roth, An Extension of Screw Theory (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - Olin Library (Box 50, Folder 53)